Lee Shu Cheng, Hadi

+65 87920504 leeshuzheng@gmail.com

Front End Engineer with a strong background in emerging web frameworks and coordinating organisational practices across vertical teams. As a developer for the world's third biggest NFT marketplace, he focuses on high fidelity prototyping and delivering sensible user experiences to end users. Adjacent to his profession, his passions lie in independent record label management and blockchain technology... or, well, watching YouTube videos about it.

EXPERIENCE

Mintable Oct 2021 - Ongoing

Front End Engineer

- Standardised all components with defensive CSS, ensuring consistent layouts for varying data types
- Successfully integrated gas-free minting options on Ethereum with platform

Cargobase Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

Front-End Developer

 Lead developer on SaaS platform upgrade, utilising React to improve user experience and load time

Ernst & Young Jan 2018 - Nov 2020 (Acquired Adelphi Digital in Nov 18)

UX Developer

- Scaled and extended functionalities for NParks' One Million Trees program on trees.sg
- Top performer in Q3 2019
- Spearheaded revamp and maintenance project for government sector portfolio with 15 websites worth value of \$250,000
- Strengthened the Science Centre website build, winning best User Experience in the 2018 Stevie Award

EDUCATION

National University of Singapore

Singapore

B.Soc.Sci. (Hons.) Communications and New Media

2013 - 2017

SKILLS

WORKING KNOWLEDGE: HTML5/CSS3, SASS, Pug, JavaScript, Typescript (React), PHP, Gulp, Webpack, Wordpress, Git Workflow

BASIC KNOWLEDGE: Python, MongoDB, MySQL